energyandfitnesshelp.com 2017-06-03

# Privacy Policy – energyandfitnesshelp.com – Health and beauty, medical and pharmaceutical discoveries

We say welcome to all the fans of energyandfitnesshelp.com to enjoy the fun. We never sell out your privacy which you provide to energyandfitnesshelp.com.

Log Files, Cookies and Web Beacons

As many other Websites, energyandfitnesshelp.com uses log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), number of clicks to analyze trends.We may permit third parties to collect user personal information over time or across third-party websites, and we may permit third parties to gather personal information passively on our websites for behavioral advertising purposes.

Statistical Information about your Visit

When you visit our sites, our computers may automatically collect statistics about your visit. This information does not identify you personally, but rather pertains to your visit to our sites. We may monitor statistics such as how many people visit our sites, the user’s IP address, which pages people visit on our sites, from which domains our visitors reach our sites, and which browsers people use. We use these statistics about your visit for aggregation purposes only. These statistics are used to help us improve the performance of our Web sites.

Disclosure by Law 

If we are required by law to disclose certain information to local, state, federal, national or international law enforcement authorities, we will do so. We will also disclose information to third parties as necessary in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations. We may share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud, or enforce or apply our agreements.

Third Party Ad Servers

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message).

We strive to keep your personal information from being accessed by unauthorized third parties by using reasonable means to safeguard it. However, as transfer of any kind of data over the internet is never 100 per cent secure, we cannot give you any guarantees and urge you to be cautious when disclosing sensitive information. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy policy periodically. We advise you to review this document from time to time.  
If you have further queries please contact us.
